Alright, the next shot you want to learn is your snap shot.
Basically, it's the difference between a wrist shot and a slap shot.
It's kind of in between there of what you're going to do.
For a snap shot, just like the wrist shot, you're going to plant yourself, put a little bend in your knees.
Get your hands on your stick.
You can stick handle.
And then all you're going to do is you're going to pull it back, just like the wrist shot, but then you're going to pull all of your weight back on to the back foot, and then you're going to transfer your weight on to the front foot.
But this time with the stick, you're going to actually snap it, you're going to snap the stick and follow through.
And sometimes that gives you a little bit harder shot than your wrist shot, your typical wrist shot.
And that's pretty much a snap shot.
It's not too difficult, but, again, the same thing, the same thing as a wrist shot, pretty much, just the extra snap.